Buy Art

More

Log out

Privacy Policy
==============

**POLICY UPDATES ARCHIVE  
‍  
‍**Privacy Policy created on 1/21/2022  
  
Last updated: 03/03/2023:  
Policy update archive and policy version section added.  
In paragraph 2, we removed the payment partner ”Klarna” in the section ”PAYMENT INFORMATION.”  
In paragraph 7, we removed the payment partner ”Klarna” in the area ”Third-Party Service Providers.”  
In paragraph 7, we replaced the text ”(Tutanota)” with ”(Mailfence).”  
In paragraph 14, we replaced the title ”14. CONTACT US” with ”14. FEEDBACK / CONTACT”.  
In paragraph 2, we added the privacy centered tools "Tiny Analytics" and "Swetrix".  
In paragraph 7, we added the word "TinyAnalytics" and a hyperlink.

**POLICY VERSION**  
  
Privacy Policy v1.3  

**FOREWORDS  
‍**  
We believe that integrity today is one of the most critical issues of modern times. The status quo for using, storing, and handling personal data needs to change to make the digital presence sustainable. The status quo for using, storing, and handling personal data needs to change to make the digital presence sustainable. Social media companies can put us in the loop of endless scrolling, and we consider them holding the biggest responsibility for this. We also believe that organizations using social media platforms for marketing and advertising should ask if their business is contributing to this endless unhealthy loop.  
  
We are not, in any way, perfect, but we try to do what we can. If you have any feedback on how we can improve integrity on this site, please get in touch with us.

**Welcome to AV Art Sweden AB!  
‍**  
AV Art Sweden AB values your privacy. This notice describes what information we collect, how we use it, and, if necessary, those with whom we share it.   
‍  
By purchasing the products, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Use of the website and purchase of the products is also subject to our Terms and Conditions.  
‍  
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of the website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. This Privacy Policy has been developed and is maintained in accordance with all applicable federal and international laws and regulations and specifically with the California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA – U.S regulation) and the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation - European regulation).

**1\. GENERAL INFORMATION  
‍**  
The personal data of the users that are collected and processed through the website:

https://www.andreasvarro.com

Will be under responsibility and in charge of:

**AV Art Sweden AB.  
Phone: +46 (0)72 328 95 10  
Info@andreasvarro.com  
‍**  
(Hereinafter referred to as AV Art Sweden AB).

‍

**2\. TYPES OF INFORMATION GATHERED  
‍**  
AV Art Sweden AB will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless AV Art Sweden AB requests it and you provide it voluntarily.  
‍  
Information You Give Us. You provide information when you search, read and watch the content, buy the products and/or communicate with us. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with the following information:  
‍  
\* First and last name  
  
\* Email address  
  
\* Phone number  
  
\* Address (shipping purposes)  
  
\* ZIP/Postal code  
  
\* Tokenised IP address  
  
\* Payment Information  
  
\* Any additional information relating to you that you provide to us directly through our website or indirectly through our website or online presence such as ‘cookies’.  
‍  
**Payment information:** Your credit card information or payment information, will be processed by “Stripe” and “PayPal” (payment platforms) which will treat and safeguard your data with total security and with the exclusive purpose of processing the purchase of the products. AV Art Sweden AB reserves the right to contract any payment platform available in the market, which treats your data for the exclusive purpose of processing the purchase of the products.  
‍  
Please consult “Stripe” and “PayPal” privacy policy here:  
  
[Paypal  
‍](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)  
‍  
**‍**

**TinyAnalytics**: We use TinyAnalytics provided by TinyAnalytics, Ltd ("TinyAnalytics"). TinyAnalytics is a data analytics platform that respects user privacy and does NOT use cookies for its operation.  
All information collected and gathered by TinyAnalytics is anonymous. This tool and technology collects and analyzes certain types of information such as device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, feature usage metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, unique mobile device identifiers and other similar information. The information generated by TinyAnalytics may be transmitted to and stored by TinyAnalytics on servers located in the European Union. We use TinyAnalytics Analytics data collection to improve the website and our service.  
See the TinyAnalytics privacy policy here:  
‍  
HYPERLINK "[https://tinyanalytics.io/privacy-policy"https://tinyanalytics.io/privacy-policy](https://tinyanalytics.io/privacy-policy%22https://tinyanalytics.io/privacy-policy)"  
Although TinyAnalytics does not store any cookies on the user's browser and is anonymous. The user can "opt-out" of this feature by visiting:  
‍  
HYPERLINK "[https://andreasvarro.com/?pixel\_optout=true" https://andreasvarro.com/?pixel\_optout=true](https://andreasvarro.com/?pixel_optout=true%22%20https://andreasvarro.com/?pixel_optout=true)"

**Swetrix Analytics:** We use Swetrix provided by Swetrix.com, Ukraine ("Swetrix"). Swetrix is a data analytics platform that respects user privacy and does NOT use cookies for its operation.  
‍  
All information collected and gathered by Swetrix is anonymous. This tool and technology collects and analyzes certain types of information such as device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, feature usage metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, unique mobile device identifiers and other similar information. The information generated by Swetrix may be transmitted to and stored by Swetrix on servers located in the European Union. We use Swetrix Analytics data collection to improve the website and our service.  
‍  
See the Swetrix privacy policy here:  
‍  
[Swetrix Policy  
‍](https://swetrix.com/privacy)  
Mailfence: We use Mailfence provided by Mailfence - ContactOffice Group sa, Belgium ("Mailfence"). Mailfence is an email service provider, with end-to-end encryption, that respects user privacy. The service is used to send communications to the user via e-mail. Mailfence does not scan e-mails to assume or send advertising and marketing. Information collected through the use of Mailfence will be collected and used in accordance with your own privacy policy and our privacy policy.  Please be informed that information stored in our e-mail systems are encrypted, but emails sent directly to us and trough our email forms are not end-to-end encrypted. To be able to send encrypted messages to us you need to use Mailfence or other similar end-to-end encryption.  
‍  
Please consult Mailfence’s privacy policy here:  

**3\. HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR DATA**  
‍  
Personal data will be kept for the time necessary for the provision of the products. The owner may be allowed to retain personal data for a longer period whenever the user has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the owner may be obliged to retain personal data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority. Once the retention period expires, personal data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.  
‍  
The information collected and indicated in section 2 (TYPES OF INFORMATION RECEIVED) of this privacy policy will be stored by AV Art Sweden AB for 1 year. After 1 year from the collection of the information, the information will be deleted from our servers and storage systems.  
‍

**4\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION.**  
‍  
In general, we use the information we collect primarily to provide, maintain, protect and improve our current website and products and to develop new products and services. We use personal information collected through our site as described below and described elsewhere in this Policy to:  
‍  
\* Identify you as a user in our system.  
  
\* User registration.  
  
\* Process your purchases and deliver the products.  
  
\* Improve our products, website, and how we operate our business.  
  
\* Improve the website.  
  
\* Respond to your comments or questions through our support team.  
  
\* Send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates,  
security alerts and support and administrative messages.  
  
\* Communicate with you about upcoming events, offers and news about products and services offered by AV Art Sweden AB and our selected partners.  
  
\* Marketing purposes of AV Art Sweden AB.  
  
\* Protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized or illegal activity.

‍

**5\. HOW DO YOU GET MY CONSENT?  
‍**  
By placing an order, communicating with us through the contact forms or our contact information and providing us with personal information to communicate with you, you consent to our collection, storage and use of your information on the terms contained in this privacy policy.  You consent to the use of cookies on the terms contained in our cookie policy (please see our cookie Policy). You may withdraw your consent by sending us your request via the contact information or the contact page.

‍

**6\. SOCIAL MEDIA  
‍**  
On our website you will find links and functions linked to different social networks, in which you can share your information.  
‍  
It is advisable to consult the privacy policy and data protection of each social network used on our website.  
‍  
[Instagram privacy policy  
‍](http://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/)

**7\. HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION  
‍**  
We are not in the business of our customers information to others. We share customer information only as described below.  
‍  
**Third-Party Service Providers.** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include process payments (Stripe, PayPal, Klarna), create the platform and host the store, deliver the products (courier companies), sending email (Mailfence), analyzing data (Swetrix), providing marketing assistance and providing search results and links.  
‍  
These third-party services and tools may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use that information for other purposes. Information shared with these third-party services will be treated and stored in accordance with their respective privacy policies and our privacy policy.  
‍  
**Business Transfers.** In the event that AV Art Sweden AB creates, merges with, or is acquired by another entity, your information will most likely be transferred. AV Art Sweden AB will email you or place a prominent notice on our Website before your information becomes subject to another privacy policy.  
‍  
**Protection of AV Art Sweden AB and others.** We release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce or apply our Terms and conditions and other agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of AV Art Sweden AB, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
‍  
**With Your Consent.** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when personally identifiable information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.  
‍  
**Anonymous Information.** AV Art Sweden AB uses the anonymous browsing information collected automatically by our servers primarily to help us administer and improve the Website. We may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about the Website to potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. This information is not personally identifiable.  
‍  
**Email Address.** The email address that you supply to us for purposes of receiving our email communications will never be rented or sold to a third party.

‍

**8\. PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION**  
  
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. If transactions are processed on the Website, transaction information is transmitted to and from the Website in encrypted form using industry-standard SSL connections to help protect such information from interception. We restrict authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide products or services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information.  
‍  
AV Art Sweden AB follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once AV Art Sweden AB receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while AV Art Sweden AB strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
‍  
We will not sell, distribute, or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

‍

**9\. EU MEMBERS’ RIGHTS (GDPR COMPLIANT)  
‍**  
If you are habitually located in the European Union, you have the right to access, rectify, download or erase your information, as well as the right to restrict and object to certain processing of your information. While some of these rights apply generally, certain rights apply only in certain limited circumstances.

We describe these rights below:  
‍  
**Access and portability:** to access and know what information is stored in our servers, you can send us your request through our contact information.  
‍  
**Rectify, Restrict, Limit, Delete:** You can also rectify, restrict, limit or delete much of your  
information.  
‍  
**Object:** When we process your information based on our legitimate interests as explained above, or in the public interest, you may object to this processing in certain circumstances. In such cases, we will stop processing your information unless we have compelling legitimate reasons to continue processing it or where it is necessary for legal reasons.  
‍  
**Revoke consent:** Where you have previously given your consent, such as to allow us to process and store your personal information, you have the right to revoke your consent to the processing and storage of your information at any time. For example, you may withdraw your consent by updating your settings. In certain cases, we may continue to process your information after you have withdrawn your consent if we have a legal basis for doing so or if your withdrawal of consent was limited to certain processing activities.  
‍  
**Complaint:** If you wish to file a complaint about our use of your information (and without prejudice to any other rights you may have), you have the right to do so with your local supervisory authority. Users can exercise all these rights by contacting us through the contact information or the contact page.  
‍  
Additionally, if you are a European resident, we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfil contracts we might have with you or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe.  
‍  
You can see more about these rights at:  
‍  

**10\. CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE (CalOPPA)  
‍**  
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared.  
‍  
Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA).  
‍  
\* According to the California Online Privacy act, you have the following rights:

\* Know what personal data is being collected.  
‍  
\* Know whether your personal data is sold or disclosed and to whom.  
  
\* Access to your personal data.  
  
\* Request to delete any personal information about you.  
  
\* Not be discriminated against for exercising their privacy rights.

**11\. CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION  
‍**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of the California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA – U.S regulation) and the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation - European regulation) regarding the protection of the personal data of minors. We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us. If we become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete that information, terminate that person's account, and restrict access to that person.

‍  
**12\. EDITING AND DELETING INFORMATION  
‍**  
If you believe that any information, we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. You can change, modify, rectify and delete your Information at any time, please contact us through the contact information. To opt-out of AV Art Sweden AB email, follow the instructions included in the email. Your request should be processed within 48 hours.

‍  
**13\. SUPPLIERS AND OTHER THIRD PARTIES  
‍**  
Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information AV Art Sweden AB collects from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether other users or suppliers on AV Art Sweden AB, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. AV Art Sweden AB does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. AV Art Sweden AB is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of other websites on the Internet, even those linked to or from the AV Art Sweden AB site. AV Art Sweden AB encourages you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.  
‍

**14\. FEEDBACK / CONTACT  
‍**  
If you have questions or concerns about these Privacy Policy and the handling and security of your data, please contact us through our contact page or through the following contact information:  
‍  
**Phone: +46 (0)72 328 95 10  
Info@andreasvarro.com**

‍

Discover more

© Andreas Varro, all rights reserved. Images on this website cannot be distributed or used, in any way, without the artist's permission. All portrait images of the artist are photographed by [Lena Larsson](https://www.lenalarsson.com/).

Log out

Navigation
